Hm.
Good morning.
Do you have any news?
I can't believe we're talking amongst ourselves.
All they said was that it was from the last shoot.
That's all they said.
That's right.
Do you all remember this?
They called us in here one by one.
We interviewed them one by one.
You don't know what each member answered, do you?
No, I don't.
Here's a summary of the VTR.
Please take a look.
Here we go.
Oh!
That's HIRO-chan.
Like that.
That's what they all look like.
So...
Why were you scared this time
Really.
It's like a room for mental illness.
I'm so nervous.
Hello.
I'm Kiamaei.
Excuse me.
I just missed my jaw.
I made a mistake with my jaw.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I like it.
We, the Batten Girls' Club, send our pink yell to the blue earth.
We are all very leaders, blue leaders.
I'm Miyu Yanagi, the nemerleien princess of Batten Girl Squad. Please give my best regards.
I'm Kitazakura, the president of Kyushu food culture lovers association of the Batten Girls Club. I am in charge of purple. Please give me your best regards.
I am Kiina Haruno, an official supporter of the Batten Girls' Club. Please give my best regards to you.
I am Kyamai, the dance leader in front of O-imo and Kaneko-san. Please give my regards to them.
I am Riko Oyada, the Karate Frame Lobby of Batten Show Figurehead, and the MC in charge of Hakkai MC for the talk.
I am on the show until November 26, 2000.
How far are you going? Did you do foot size or something?
I'm 23.5cm and about 158cm tall,
They made me talk the best I could.
I'm confronting a female student.
I didn't even ask what we were doing.
Did they call you anyway? I got some kind of call.
What's going on?
I don't know.
What is it?
I want it.
Okay, so...
So you all were called in without knowing anything about it.
How did it go? At that time...
It was kind of scary, wasn't it?
I was scared, so scared.
I thought something was going to come out from behind me.
I mean, I was already doing a 360.
I thought, "They're going to notice me. I'm just getting started.
I know I cut a lot of this out.
It took me a long time to sit down.
It took me a long time to get in.
So here's the quiz.
I'm doing it separately.
Oh, it's me.
Me?
Why?
Why not?
I'm on a diet and I ate pasta today.
You said you were going on a diet, but Masai eats helmac?
And his squire.
What do you like best?
Strawberries.
Tomatoes.
Meat, rice, garlic and almonds.
Sweet potatoes.
But I also like biko.
I like yams, like nazaimo.
I also like mebaneram with okra and other things on top.
Delicious!
I think the charm of Kyushu
I think the charm of Kyushu is that it's all packed into one group.
We are all from Kyushu.
Fukuoka and Nagasaki.
That's why we love Kyushu.
I hope we can convey the charm of Kyushu to the world.
What is one word you would use to describe Wattenshoe?
I don't know... one word.
One word.
Kyushu
Love
Healing
Watten
Difficult
difficult
Difficult this
Looks like a long time.
You said it about 8.6 times.
Wait, wait, wait.
It wasn't one word, was it?
It was a sentence, right?
It was a sentence.
What?
Yes, I think Ai wrote this.
A group of six girls.
Oh!
Ai-chan would have said
Jaan!
I'm glad you all like taro.
I have one word for you.
Yes.
I say I'm glad.
I'm a little bit like Kiina, the six girls who know an apricot when they see one.
I think you'll know it when you see it, but you're going to say it.
I can tell.
Ai, you are the apricot of the sweet potato world.
Are you saying that?
I think so.
Ai-chan loves Kyushu, and Kyushu is a six-person toyro.
Oh, Yurukun.
He said something like 6 pieces 1.
Oh, I thought you would say something like 6 people toiro.
Thanks.
Herself.
I don't know if I'm right, but Hon.
What I think love said was, home.
Oh, it was short.
It was short.
I could tell.
How did you get into the batten?
It's something, isn't it? I wonder.
Answer.
Please.
Q!
What?
The kanji
Scary, scary.
Why?
You really did say one word.
Yes, I did.
It was a Q.
Q. Too long.
Too long.
That was delicious.
I also put a little batten on it while I was saying the last group was in old Chinese characters.
So I got fooled.
I got fooled.
Oh, no.
I did the right thing.
I think it looks like pudding a la mode,
It's like all kinds of fruits, all kinds of personalities, and it's cute at the same time,
So..,
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Ehhhh...
What is it?
It's so deep!
It looks like a pudding... or a mode... if you eat it...
What is it?
It's food!
It's food, isn't it?
I thought you said it was deep.
It looks like a pudding or something.
Pork bone ramen
I thought it might be a food with a gap
I thought you like Sakura Ramen.
I looked forward to it.
It looks like pudding a la mode. When you eat it, it's thick pork bone ramen.
Nice, isn't it?
Sakura likes it and so do I.
Common point.
It looks like pudding a la mode. But when you eat it, it's garlic.
When you eat garlic, it reminds you that you ate it yesterday, right?
I think the garlic is mentioned in a way that it is that deep.
It looks like pudding a la mode. When you eat it, it looks like coffee milk.
I don't know.
I chose coffee, but I thought milk is a drink.
Milk is a drink.
Coffee jelly.
You wanted to drink Jell-O?
Coffee.
Coffee milk.
It looks like pudding a la mode. But when you eat it, it's spicy like wasabi.
What do you mean?
Did you have a moment like this?
It's scary, but there's also a deep and spicy part of you.
That's not what I mean.
I see.
The man himself.
It looks like pudding a la mode. But when you eat it, it's a hotpot.
Motsu-nabe.
It's too bad.
With a sense of Fukuoka.
A little.
It's cute, but if you eat it, it's like motsu nabe.
It's quite deep.
I think we've done a lot so far.
There is the best tasting motsu nabe that has been stewed in a lot of broth,
I think that's the mode now.
It's amazing.
Really?
Delicious.
Interesting.
Congratulations.
That's a nice word.
Yes, it is.
It sounds good.
I want to keep saying them, from now on.
Memories of places that remain in your heart.
The 6th anniversary of the first VANVAN live after Lila and I joined the group, we all worked so hard together.
I also worked very hard while worrying about various things, so I think it was a memorable experience for me.
It was the time we performed at the Japan Expo in Paris, France,
There was no stage direction at all at that live performance, just the music and the audience who knew us for the first time got excited together,
I was impressed that people who knew us for the first time got really excited with us.
Is there a skill that you have that no one else has?
A special skill?
I can sleep anywhere for 3 seconds.
It's a special skill.
I'm awake now.
I am good at eating a lot.
I'm not so sure, though, because I ate a piece of pasta today and I was full,
But I can usually finish a bowl of pork ramen, kaedama, or midama with great relish.
I think I have a good palate.
Taste?
I am fine. I'm really energetic from morning till night, and I'm full of energy.
It's a little difficult to draw, but I can do it.
I can do it.
What is your special skill that we don't know anything about?
I think I might have figured it out.
I think I got it.
How about you, Riko? Do you think everyone knows?
I know everyone, but I have mentioned some of my specialties,
I'd like you to choose one out of them.
One?
One.
I can put my pinky toe on my ring finger. I think this is it.
I also put my pinky toe on my ring finger.
I am the same, and to put the little toe of the foot on the ring toe.
The leader puts the ring toe of the toe on the ring toe.
I don't know.
I'm unconscious of the fact that Riko's special skill is putting her pinky toe on her toes.
Yeah, I'm telling it like it is.
I can put my pinky toe on my ring finger without using my hand, which is roughly the same as everyone else's.
Is it the pinky toe or the ring finger?
Either one.
I can put my pinky toe on my ring finger without using my hand!
Wow, wow, wow.
That's great!
Can you do it?
Do I have a good foot?
It looks like this.
You can put it like this.
By the way, you can put both legs on like this.
I've done it all.
When we are always together...
Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh no!
You can imitate a goat.
I don't know where this is.
When I was in Cambodia, I saw an animal that looked like a goat,
I was wondering, maybe it was a goat, and there was a goat, and, uh, we greeted each other.
With this.
I'll put the beam in, so, uh, what?
I don't have a note. One thing.
What? A member secret?
One of our members, Kiina Haruno.
We often share the same room at hotels,
We usually spend time together, but I don't know a single word about her at the hotel.
Sometimes I wonder what she is doing, and I always ask her about her report.
Heh.
Sakura's entertainment in the hotel is not through the earphones, but through the speakers.
I'll say.
I'm probably the only one who knows this.
I'm the one who lives in the room.
The other day, Sakura and I went out for hamburgers,
She is famous for eating a big meal, isn't she?
A hamburger set meal? A set?
Everyone ordered a set, but Sakura-chan didn't order rice.
But she got rice by mistake, even though she didn't ask for it,
Sakura-chan said, "But that's God's way of telling us to eat,
So Sakura-chan said, "God already told me to eat it," and she ate it.
There were sweets we had at home,
Her mother told her to share them with everyone,
But she ate all the leftovers.
I ate it with a pin.
It was dead.
It's a very, very candy.
I wonder if he ever dyed that hair.
When I was about five years old.
What? That's when it happened.
I raised him, too.
I've had it cooled down a little bit.
I think pretty much everyone in the place has an image of black hair
Actually, a little bit.
I just remembered my secret.
Did I tell you?
I don't know if it's a secret.
What is it?
The secret that you haven't told the members.
I don't remember.
What?
What is it?
Lila's secret.
It's your secret.
It might be sad if it's this one,
I actually like Shine Muscat more than strawberries.
I say I like strawberries, but actually I like muscats.
I can't eat green peppers either.
I've been saying that a lot, but it's like cana peppers.
Cana peppers.
Actually, I can't eat green peppers like a 5 year old.
I can't eat it.
In his special skills, he writes that he can dance the Isawa Yuki Wakataka Gundan, but he can't write the character for hawk.
How about this?
I don't like this kind of Rirua-chan, but actually, I don't like it inside me.
I hate it.
I've been telling her that I care about her.
When I left the house today, I was going to go right, but I went left.
Sweat in the air.
I'm not lucky.
I'm lucky.
When you're running a little late, you don't rush.
What?
Even if it's late?
When it's late, I'm not in a hurry.
So it's late anyway.
I understand.
I wonder.
Let's try again if I'm wrong.
Did I say that?
I'm losing a lot of height.
I don't know if it's a secret, but I'm 158cm,
I don't know if it's a secret, but I'm 158 cm, but I've shrunk so much that I'm not 158 cm anymore.
Why?
157.6 cm?
That much?
I shrunk a lot.
You did?
I did it! I'm so tall!
So I've shrunk in height.
I see.
So you think it's going to change your height?
I think it's going to change, right?
I'm going to be replaced by Sakura and the others, aren't I?
No, I'll be fine.
This is a program in which Batten Shoujo-tai will deliver variety shows, on-location shooting, and behind-the-scenes documentaries of their live performances.
It will be a Nukasa-original broadcasting station that will offer a variety of genres in addition to variety,
We haven't decided on a title yet.
We have not decided on a title yet.
Please think about it.
Wow.
Yes, of course.
Oh, wow.
Looks like fun.
You're not good at this kind of thing, are you?
If I think about this or something, it could really be a title.
Yeah.
You do a lot of things, don't you?
Even if it's not something like 575.
Why is this 575?
575?
I don't know.
Why is there still no overlap between each of them?
It's fine.
It's cute and fun to be near the stage all the time.
I'm so scared.
It's like being by my side.
Always by my side.
I thought I'd get to see a different side of him.
I thought you'd see a different side of me.
Different sides.
Cute.
It doesn't mean what you think it means.
You're right.
When I say "cute and fun,
I've created a personality I didn't know I had.
I'm pretty sure no one told you.
The title I came up with was,
Ta-da!
24 hours behind the scenes of the Batten Girls!
Yes!
That's a little harsh.
We've been together for a long time,
We have been together for a long time, so I thought it would be great if we could show them 24 hours of our lives,
I thought it would be great if I could show them 24 hours on this show.
The Batten Girls' Band,
Oh, my gosh!
LOL!
I made the title call in a slightly pokey way.
The important part.
I went to the concert!
We're going in today.
You're letting me in?
Suddenly, Watten Shoujo-tai hysteria!
It's scary.
It's like a love story all of a sudden.
That's what we did.
In case you don't know the rules, Watten Shoujo-tai...
No?
One more time. One more time.
Huh?
Well, then...
Why did you go with that?
Because it was 575, and 1,000 wasn't enough, so I put 2 on it anyway, and Watten Shoujo-tai...
I had to put it in, so put it in,
Hysteria is,
Watten Girls University is probably 8 letters.
So, hysteria is like 4 letters,
Add it up, and you get 575.
What is hysteria?
Hysteria, something,
Behind the scenes, documentary,
Tally, hysterical.
Hysterical, sensual.
Hysteria is..,
Hysteria.
Psychic.
No. You call it neutic?
The other side of enginstai.
What do you think?
The front face of Engines Thai
I think most of you see this on stage,
But I read that we will be following closely behind the scenes of variety shows, location shoots, and live performances,
So, I was wondering if you would like to see the variety of her on location and during variety shows,
I was like, "Wow, I didn't know this girl had this side of her.
I don't mean "behind-the-scenes" in a good way.
I see.
You may have heard that somewhere,
I was thinking of Battenbutten for the Battenwomen,
But maybe that's a little too close.
Too close?
You said you've heard it somewhere.
We already knew it.
Wow.
It's a chronological thing.
Maybe it has something to do with the age.
So they are that close.
Mile after mile of the Batten Girls.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's not like they're close or anything.
It's close.
Batten Girls' Club, look at this.
They're cute.
You want to know about the Batten Girls Club?
Oh, no.
Oh, man.
It's like they're doing it.
It's just an image.
Batten Shoujo-tai's Batten Q
Gatte-Q.
Aaah!
Batten Shoujo-tai's Kyushu, Everybody Q
Can't give out the title?
Why don't you give it to me when it's your time?
This is what I wanted to see.
The correct answer is X small itself, try X.
It's close, but I don't know the original.
I don't know the original.
Rira-chan, are you strange?
Oh, by the way, it's three hundred.
I've heard of it somewhere, but I thought it would be nice to try Batten for Batten women, but their mouths are a little too close together.
It's a little out.
But it's nice, isn't it?
It was great.
It was interesting.
How did everyone like it?
It was really interesting.
I got to know some things I didn't know before.
So, really.
I would like to decide on the title of the program here.
Ah...
Is this okay with you all?
Yes.
What's going on?
Why are there so many people in the room?
I want to make a hashtag or something, don't I?
Yes, that's right.
Then, let's put them all out at once.
Let's all do it at once.
Let's do it!
Let's try it out, back face, back face, try it out, back face, try it out, suddenly back face.
What?
It's almost 3-3.
Wow, that's great.
I had one more person in the mix.
Suddenly, the other side.
It's 3-3.
Surprisingly.
So you want to mix it up with two others?
Sure, sure, sure.
Try the other side.
Turn it over.
It's good, isn't it? Back side?
I see.
If you turn it over, it looks like this.
It looks like it could be posed like this.
Yes, indeed.
Turn it over and see the batten.
I see.
Is that okay?
All right.
Turn over the batten girls' group.
Batten Girls' Squad. Turn over and batten.